women should be paid twice as much as
men shut up
libtard go away
loser I am drinking your liberal
tears stop are you sick and tired of
trolls ruining your social media
experience yes well then the troll
cliche Wiki is for you when a troll
attacks with an insult you've heard a
thousand times before triggered much
delete your account Don't Waste
Your Time arguing with them just head on
over to troll cliches. comom find the
cliche that your trolls been engaging in
copy and paste that hot URL and then
send him the
link what it's that easy it's that easy
shut the up snowflake but what if
the troll keeps responding well I wish I
thought of that possibility I
did now you just send him a second URL
one that says you've already lost this
argument just keep sending them the link
again and again and again again no and
again I'm not triggered and
again your gender gives you a lower
IQ and again make these stuns oh f
and
eventually they'll go away for good very
cool very cool indeed troll
cliches. try it
today